const data = [
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ea9",
    correctAnswer: "J. K. Rowling",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Christopher Tolkien", "Philip Pullman", "C. S. Lewis"],
    question: "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter and the Cursed Child'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: ["G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ea9",
    correctAnswer: "J. K. Rowling",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Christopher Tolkien", "Philip Pullman", "C. S. Lewis"],
    question: "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter and the Cursed Child'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
},
{
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f36",
    correctAnswer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    incorrectAnswers: [
    "G. K. Chesterton",
    "Philip Pullman",
    "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice"
}
]

export default data;